sentenceseek.com 2013-05-22

# FyberSearch Assist - Privacy Policy

|       |    
This website, all sub-domains/pages of any website owned by FyberSearch and all contents of all web pages owned by FyberSearch will be referred to as "FyberSearch" in the remainder of this privacy policy. 

Information that FyberSearch Collects 

FyberSearch may collect and save the following information: 
* Your computer's IP Address.
* One or more unique visitor/session id numbers tracked via cookies and/or web beacons.
* The files you view while using this website and when you visited them.
* The web browser you are using.
* Your search settings.
* Information you enter into any forms on this website.
* The URL you were at that referred you to this website.
* Other information about the computer you are using and it's settings transmitted when you visit FyberSearch or read our emails.

How the Collected Information is Used 

FyberSearch may use the above information in the following ways: 
* All information may be used to create statistics that will be shown to certain individuals as well as the public. These statistics will not include your email address or your computer IP address.
* FyberSearch does not rent or sale your email address or computer IP address. There may be certain times where the release of this type of information to another person and/or business is required by a court order or to complete a job that FyberSearch has assigned a person and/or business such as generating website traffic statistics.
* FyberSearch may share the information we collect with third parties in order to meet certain obligations of our corporate relationships. For example, we generate revenue using third party ad systems like AdSense, XML Ad feed providers, ISEDN.org, etc. To effectively target advertising to content the information we collect from users as discussed above will need to be disclosed.
* FyberSearch will not be held responsible for any circumstances that are out of the control of FyberSearch that result in a violation of this privacy policy. Examples of these situations: people illegally breaking into this website, software malfunction and/or equipment malfunction.

* When you use your email address to sign up for one of our services/tools you should receive email from us. Unless you sign up for our newsletter or member's account you should not receive more than a few emails pertaining to the service you signed up for. All of the emails we send should relate to the service you requested. We do not send unsolicited bulk email to our users and we do not buy mailing lists. 
* The following is an example of why we may send you a few emails when using one of our services. Depending on various circumstances this exact scenario may be different for you.   
Example: You sign up for one of our services and receive an email after completing the first form and after completing your payment. You then receive an email confirming that we performed the requested service and possibly receive a follow up email asking you how you liked our service.
* If you sign up to receive the FyberSearch newsletter you should only receive periodic copies of the newsletter. This newsletter is primarily non-commercial and serves as a way for FyberSearch to communicate to interested parties about the developments we are making. If you have unsubscribed but still received another copy of the newsletter it was not intentional on our part. You should immediately tell us about the problem so we can look into it and immediately correct the problem.
* If you have a member's account you may receive periodic emails relating to your account and any updates that we make.

* This privacy policy is a part of our terms of service.

* Please contact FyberSearch if you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy.
|       |
